cummins.com 2017-05-10

# Website Privacy Policy | Cummins

Thank you for visiting this website, which is owned and operated by Cummins Inc. This Privacy Policy contains our online privacy and security practices and describes the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Information We Collect**  
You may use our website without providing any information about yourself. However, in order to provide some of our web based services to you or to permit you to enter certain sections of our website, we require you to provide a small amount of personal information. For example, if you want to register a product, submit a question to us, inquire about our products, sign up for one of our programs, purchase items via our online store, or apply for a job at one of our offices, we must collect some personal information about you. We also provide certain sections of our sites for our suppliers, which allow them to access their Cummins account.

Occasionally, we may invite you to participate in a survey or poll such as providing feedback about our site content, services, or products. Your responses will be anonymous unless you choose to provide your contact details so that we can provide you with additional information regarding the survey.

The personal information you provide to us through our site varies, based upon the type of service you are requesting. If you choose to register for one of our programs, you always have the option of unsubscribing at any time.

**Sharing Your Information**  
We use the information you provide to us to address your request, process your order, or respond to your questions. We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries, joint ventures, affiliates, authorized distributors and other business partners, to the extent that they are assisting Cummins in fulfilling your request or providing products or services to our customers.

Cummins does not sell or share personal information provided to us with third parties for their own separate use.

**Cross-Border Transfers of Personal Information**  
Like most global organizations, Cummins transfers (shares) some of the personal data that it collects and processes with relevant affiliates (personnel) in other countries. In addition, as may be warranted for legitimate business activities, it may also share some of that information with approved business partners who provide services to Cummins and are located in other countries. The data privacy laws that apply to personal data differ from country to country, and do not always offer a consistent level of protection to data that is transferred out of the country of origin. Nevertheless, Cummins takes steps to ensure that the personal data which is transferred to other countries is adequately protected at all times by the recipient, regardless of the country and the data protection requirements required by law in that location. The protections include, for example, ensuring proper written agreements and surrounding awareness materials for transfers within the Cummins group as well as to external business partners. If you have questions about Cummins’ cross-border transfers or believe that your information has been mismanaged, you can email us at [law.department@cummins.com](mailto:law.department@cummins.com), or write to us at Cummins Inc., 500 Jackson Street, Columbus, Indiana USA 47201.

**Cookies and Other Anonymous Web Tracking Techniques**  
Like most websites, we may also collect information online through “cookies”, which are pieces of information stored directly on the computer you are using. Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit our site or information that allows customization of our site for your use. We use cookies to display information more effectively to you and to gather data about the usage of our site. You can always set your browser to refuse all cookies or to warn you when a cookie is sent to you. This will provide you with more control over the acceptance of cookies on your computer. However, it is possible that some portions of this website will not function properly or may perform more slowly if you choose to reject cookies.

**Safeguarding Your Information**  
Cummins has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure the information we collect online from loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access, or theft. This includes appropriate safeguards for customers making purchases through our sites, as well as those who enroll in our programs.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
This website is not intended to collect or maintain any information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we collected any information from anyone under the age of 13, we will purge it immediately, except for responding to a question or inquiry on a one-time basis from the individual.

**Right of Access, Correction, and Objection/Consent**  
We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information on file with us is accurate and up-to-date. In that regard, we invite you to contact us to update your information if it changes, such as your email address, so that you can continue to receive information from us that you have requested.

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or operated by Cummins. You should carefully review the privacy policies and practices of other websites, as we cannot control and are not responsible for privacy policies or practices of third-party websites that are not ours.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
As we continue to provide additional services and as the privacy laws and regulations evolve, it may be necessary to revise or update our Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way the notification information that we have available. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

We will always use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Contact Us**  
If you have questions about Cummins’ Safe Harbor Privacy Procedures or practices or believe that your information has been mismanaged, you can contact us by emailing us at [law.department@cummins.com](mailto:law.department@cummins.com), or writing to us at Cummins Inc. Global Headquarters, 500 Jackson Street, Columbus, IN 47201.

Updated February 2017
